[{"topicId":"14","id":"14000","langCode":"en","question":"OBmbgF/o/bNq3ZHSrL62zA65mBhrV+0O32yAlVy0c+raC+57DOq9ZI39/G368IeI","answers":["both","so","but","yet"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15XdbqlLVu03bWc8GJinJJNpOL+qUmVZczLv1OQrEefLmcsN9dBgR9wjU9gR4VVgCJNObP6VQR4XMO2qHVFPVbTpuBzMhSxS2Pw3NzbVnuYh+gSQDWHtMi/Y6jNIDTjwAQXMRX65d8eOZSdyKVdKnKTHYpLCy9ssd1BrnQwAk1bHHOwyy8h4nC5PH0qkwA7tIE1xEZvJAX914xErkYJOXIczb0OsdnSCIpatkj6v0Eme9/Y+tG68OB1uSkrCIzK5N8fERXz5Og7lgC41JLfHnZdw+dD6ahyOa3S0dIOaERRNHqoC4YdQYe6UtsBWWWRx+rcZzhcn34rYo/vbaGDDiHbM1JcL28hLwE1kPAhW/AyHkiurIl8pMl+4CcUe8wua/EWE1LQmTCHnG1aVJlJOFW/LQAKtAbKVHX9SJN92rABShkHo6Moe4Ci7BLYdxib8UkI5vDtMhAGzXo1H/YTH4Yw\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14001","langCode":"en","question":"/dOp/JBtoSdA4r9w40fWUZn03civ+PSKG3bi3uaq+E1UmJqZlUmvnixdweKSD73TzHds2CUGmsWhgGaed+jTXqw+5AZcELkrvfdvWbAr1+u23ZGDX/IZqytgG2EMmmGxfKxQZK1HiIGuAuzgIwgNZ3UlYL2R2VHhywedijF+VXY0hNcWM6MBoN5TvmIa4WF1Q4gaX/7PQmZ4q58uHeXDfw\u003d\u003d","answers":["but","before","and","yet"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16G/sgtoy5ruXwfN36/JvUqBrLgfmatnR9dp9vOJpiQspiOtY5gXPgdfTLMmSbGjgGZ9xdgF5UZnQyBIPO78SKbDug3tM+i6y47LGcms9exvC1ygXR0PFUW6sdIsmtSvKxBDZ/fKscWCOi1gfUmR/hng/1ewjrC7aMlyEi8JSprtLI8H/yHj8Kk6t97RMzL/mfvJPr4YqsvdKfdLVmCvW90IvKe+u3dJNNuihVN79fPQnX3n1S1dqdyU4P0+W92KshJufnetwv0MmG0WsZMOhDxS0uvejP6t74Mmbem0pzbM+Ls2z324N843qsAo3A7P66bP5YY2QbsKtZv0wHvM+OoPuSbDiMAPM56pN3xSlMzsTxRtbG+dXNhbFkoDfX0ZL5kQVT4wpgZY5/uYgHXXHNozTU0nMspeTPWowo3j1dx2gv9/4/JFur09Up2XqdzjGkEDMunLTsXkO0UkPWTE4JrWl7iopR3EYaEtO3AHeq0rO+wr2ZLXEylBNosC+i/UDsiiqUW5RoHq1mcztiHYLHufaYWqx2//G1RW1Knv+Qe2kNSYUPxyH0JWdShlOW/ihMCAoy7k8VQgKePKNevUQEL7+wOCshJUdtM82eHxRw0cpszKaU34V4VvbJXlFa4TPJ0U9IUW8qgP2/WHRSoBs04\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14002","langCode":"en","question":"WWWL8zjnz2NBMnQvTeCM6Eb+qY2NMxxILyrDaedUuF6t0UNYn+YPAOduUABdI91EFq1LyGCs6BnXGgX6iOwG/qvyGT/sm9J0/b5KZhV3qMLmEqwRnbWjXxkDhkfcw5tDlnCQakyNb3rHTsVbEJ9qfA\u003d\u003d","answers":["so","but","for","or"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11dqActS5Fhn7lFBumhCCQQ/GpzyWWBK8+wCO0u+3/aumv+pgA+//9b1WKjsJvbIZVv9uexOLNW1t+3tWqdPomlyGZNnQn6U2ZWTVHAHYYEPXwYYqRRNj3HNz1KNhCNtrsN2NPe1aZIVopSKqmJaPwCxa8B8nP+5Ou1hyACs/AXAGQ/0CQEzIkvevn91hMn9hsfOjHKtbX/s+usrCEhxpXw2BXnfp71+aUrPb+mTTfR4MdSsQpDiY5h3Ynp0ckfSupgh5s5Jl/docLER4XT7nMeSbQbgF4P7zSfN1cUQn86yAb5/AD77fLLZMqZJHcJ8zaHILBc847TOkVFsNsA6ZAqqC6GJbwP93TFCcN7NP3Bx0NG6YqQAthRNdDgtHSjX3JC8B03GcvNM/V8+zSaFo9m2RCVFoOJg9wAKkp6dHDQe2Kz1hPZ+Ya+knbXBjNuIdFkmalmDG8ubEmr8Jh9+muXDuHkwT96FJG+4AjhsuDS2"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14003","langCode":"en","question":"kSvbtXAGtq9LMxoef2q6meecuXqBS5h9VtuIb0s5v77rv7rodKCFshzTz9k+rPpBrGlrofr0I2ldRcMIAF7Trw\u003d\u003d","answers":["for","or","so","yet"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wQQCJTp0g2dod8Rb+XgZ9bsWH3T4Bhrnq9/8yU6kTHWifGnuwVcHyn4qVskbz3Qv1otESRHy7Vdghu+gXGPqyh+GBOh2bn0LuY7S9RjT3f8cKYFlgBYJ63QXoKPH508ieD47bI4rVsY7lfsUevp7zCaiq09W+Y4ZM8nHGg2ftGvRYTUtCZMIecbVpUmUk4Vb8tAAq0BspUdf1Ik33asAFKGQejoyh7gKLsEth3GJvxS9qUJzxsNbuwDVXIohTDwbIcDZ1GQiflTcuc61JqCHvp4BjLPZgiUvBU4ceD61KO+jzSkIyZuoGDcwO/bqhHNLXUL3g6sxj3ZXrUyCzE1OQf6k5lDO8R1qMs5gEck5woRn2TafeVnRcWuLGNvv/vJYtj8VJDwPWNSCDuDtFPIE1LluUvdYoP2sQqz5+3J1dfG4+VPJeWMJomCMfvcAXModuhO5/JEvtn728XugPESI4Rskt31ogB7s035IF1Rf44/OvJlJRN1KQ5PmiwVCDjDFpwh1+Xiezzs/oVmwoVI7Q7/hynRgQrvi4Brh+PKFa/WjY/y9um2nd+IMxdeIc69SA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14004","langCode":"en","question":"CT5JVr6JpUa7N0/xn1/gkrHCG8PA06nnRq1BeytM7Ucw4pf3NgVXKoXKZHwMM/i+RNf5Dsnq8rPemzycCjDShw\u003d\u003d","answers":["for","so","nor","but"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15Hx26nKNYRDfFqGCmHWZMBruUCRMcW6gz7W3F5MWUhOSLw5+yVJaZLxkJPG/pG0HULQJntg3J7k33L4DqTNei370xywDaKcKxI3J7QS9WmBCsUoNeQtDDpX7sUGUoTMFZnOF8oqXQCcb/ID+Dk2IJ+FaYqBlxThuliVP6YLGvdhW1i5PBrvb2k8t1ak3Ed2eP/MJPOu4sIpC3fQGGMwjp2w8th7eQn0cdSSOPrZh363QNdiEuPpAq2bO1eWIv7F6iaZ9PlyiUzE5M3jOl9qn6olaCfngovX9YtFQrhh43kHRGIYrytT9mJCgx1eRi2nKBMicrm9ezSKG83GNdRP4teaOMwiMlxxWzbPV928XkDrBqRbw0FtMUBacBKY3FRd6hMttGVW4HblDXBs+XKlBV/GyD3fWVjCTAw89BgU1glKseUZk51C7sW0L8MrMjQcJoXWv4EHecaHpiUE/4Gx5pfvAicS/qmVYD6JrkK3bY8y2U5/r6j9WafGRi6Fl8rsI7agGtVh/dRrX48k5ocHNkLamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14005","langCode":"en","question":"Jn+dGFW8yKF6tAs7I3TEaGOmqlD3ms6V/DEAASGmwo0+cxQAON8iqozmU1nOfXc5ddpDJ/QonEEv5gMAeU4tEw\u003d\u003d","answers":["so","or","but","for"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13gQ2f+ysYZCED/zT7L6d0clzWKuNg6XNkn4wlg07Q5fmD+0DrKMOwZb65Gql2bBnW/1Sd5uEaXSKBuODqB8bay8rwJGqfpNxb6n6w4pfEPYeIu9E1/d+TgZM4GaL8qbXC6TaGlMXFawFepT0l/KwQTMwrN10CknXt08zRMgnZuwgNO0CeRqDWQq2rZWqDLwbjdAfvclyGVIELjqRdOiEyumrppsNjych/PA3eprN2iwhuS2UxQXfN78VP21jbHQIZ3tPBMNHYr+S4cVtaowVfjh62xjGJOxwKUzi+0zjOrUtLAbSWsgWozUNQakRTg9bB7NcW5NjPaYFHC+LlXbaYtsev9NfRcEuLppDzBGBdHuCEkyAtdIFbPqu0Wya1ZBc2J4Il1z8OGMF4muACp7AaCrhNREunuFEFCUMmyPYWTcBDFluPCSJNVqpipNI7qK5x9STpsrrpW33s0bZT7AVkguae6Hdw6S4ipw1P+jwc99"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14006","langCode":"en","question":"HgH2MGEF8XXiNcvy9F0H0Owv6/hHF6Xt5kst9tWEu5lPWQNuyPiKaBZFBnagTr6/cUHtSjZUkubxx3X1DCd221SAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["so","yet","but","and"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xAAXDi/5hzT9A0ce7/ML6JehIhHIXO+1MmUNzmgGC29U/iTx7efO3W00aMx/6+yB1gj8F9/UVIG4HpEnDqdZ9FD03st6yW/8PNaGWKuG9S4nphRmkGTpGUSCkx3NzOA/ugIAjJ4KPPoV1SUBzxLnnyFZl4VXyrsLP0h+HzRVKMxpf7QfEUSAHv8N+CY+dC/w2Z9xdgF5UZnQyBIPO78SKbDug3tM+i6y47LGcms9exvC1ygXR0PFUW6sdIsmtSvKxN/qLXn5bnKMgvvsvptAumecfgCm1weOZHI2cK3BqS7UwZW+joRoKyMpf2Un7QLaMGLIysxV1DmmWqfUqjt9cJL4hAW09lBEaORGzWzYA2E1LMugQ1lViyO5WsYYRImF1y8t8EK5kVDtUCYAbp74sQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14007","langCode":"en","question":"j4PpK7/U+A5n2atxKm94zRM7d1ZViOkyipPKhPGfm6vEXHooJIY93n9kPR2orOXGRDoDlUkCKH+RDYSdu7yxJw\u003d\u003d","answers":["yet","so","but","or"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x10LQybAaxxZJJupAn4/LWT9tS9hvt4Oa4I5Ccw3ey/zLAJYUJG9gDj2bmDClaUGyExPgXZpxz6xtGvSCwSskTTWTMKoYQzjlvLzEo5kt9amVK3hGMfS8vXv4plknienUh8NTh8b7E7956DmOD7cpGRz1Tyawn3LgprrROFdtIEzVDr+WP7vojftldPChuRyf5H7nwQZne78qi1EpSOfzV6bdMx+JuYlQapqxeC6gy/BRx86Mcq1tf+z66ysISHGlfDYFed+nvX5pSs9v6ZNN9Hgx1KxCkOJjmHdienRyR9K6mCHmzkmX92hwsRHhdPucx5JtBuAXg/vNJ83VxRCfzrLRELZvmthNSmKW6YIfme1NCl/jlZ46wH5+dL/vPPIXISJ6waulMnQ0nBrHfBdLa9sI5N+xWvJXlb77JRJDav8+Ger6HZmAgWWXng+KrIhb1tjpxB+Wv/9R+PF1OowqbWykMAi+AQCXdhj58YPfeNlizCfEdvIfPzaTIxVNCc4xOw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14008","langCode":"en","question":"jr94rRdZSzaN55QGhuDHHrMSh0v9/UHVUXK/c1AH4KXMULI4B2zSPLtnhqw5Z2feIaQWOLPrj5cM2e2uJI941GtaFBgEL2p02at2r+m0lHs\u003d","answers":["although","but","so","after"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wqtj6JySJRNB7zPP01LUMJ8QlYNvPXy0GAUnP57WG2xyimz0oewA33ugDrArJlDJpN8EkJe8trIbIQmkDdVtYLHBh60mLA8hSqvCpKxHlIieIu9E1/d+TgZM4GaL8qbXC6TaGlMXFawFepT0l/KwQRMkXpqCsqyYozRxk2bpwCxHAZCZ5OcV/Sx7dOzbj+r5z0o8wZz3LpFalaQFqm1yoyt+ooFvL0JhbJM/0k/QXJ11hVsMFx8/6P4BK7xiRYvSwxBjC0ZtuPAQP+vFOLFLIT8plWUXi6CAmuNVXF6ncpqvz7tQbze3+kLwYzocAT/+UU9H5tZtxhSqtmrv9VWmr+mCNuJqrcWsghZWNtRxw1qe+Lib5B7/TymuddCM2kndfX0l6HF+9vZZTYqvMcZlXryyJ09hz6An9nsZCKhF1T31aNNfrirKIGj4hiCvJzqzD5n/G3xE8FOlU6gDSXWcCh8Oo9PC2MfDJeU0r54rEQZiLgxG2PFx+LzxHB2mRYT1g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14009","langCode":"en","question":"yvTvcMx9d4REPSOraqMJOj8HdEU7eGDqTcF17a2WiqXy0GQjDRDXGJSeQ5+93cxW7WRYfVzfihfWGL5zM8UVWIRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d","answers":["or","although","so","and"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x126mC28PGCJ0nTpTN3F8Nw2mu9wa1Q0f4czTe0eG4eA+0qcl0rJFLCxuJTxDEgcHuebv+HlUAsukWS0+p/eNOawlH/mFv9w7Lk8A4l8WG340m0ghc54v26s9OSCbeGTiASYkBLgyjIvNvRopJdiXxyGLjFdkxzOICz9Zo/Md6k+rEgmc5ziUQQG1T6B4RwtsaZbwdH4H0kbAcOipPKQ2boJyLZaIdgmmqBqndUsTQ3Rq2f2QXCzw9CnUahYQ9gx0K5Jsw01tteoVEMYd/1oGTfva7VXImyCEbPwc2Sj9DoO9VSbXPVJ4CmICfZW61wpa9gXnHFt2D5FOl0PUOMHkZnGmQUrNnhQ6IaDWXgULguwNVx0RIYLGYJNi5TTQ3gK93OIfQH2eTrFdNkjQ8HrUCb31sicvxu3WJRKVqWYlfRk7paY4wDZMwGT+qADA8xPg/rS1Qq8ZnZfpPbqHH3pXznnHx9sn5Al9iWCno8xI03lCyQyvwakli8wxl28OrwBjRmCQ4goUiCVvOAKeF4FR3WhPyIlVhb3Z9qxCmBfs2aL196Qj/bdWK3s8sjt16iMZCwi8IkpUMn9ygoICaXQtmRGUwGk2RtAKvl9NnqpQY8mO2ZHHmeaZORawDbDrD9IeIaoClooLSm5xJYCRhzon7Hg\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14010","langCode":"en","question":"xunZ3UWkEX3HtZHj3W56FTcRIXUSYg8/1e3mQAmFpnZQh8IwEGr/VqfLZqufseO3","answers":["before","although","or","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x151vxdYzFRw04G+uJQYzKvhwmsIzV1c5PYCPEb0h0XE70eWnSraPujxyVAv6+LKU/E6IQ/BVqwnOY1AdzONAh5+7ctoBbSoQDER2TcqNGqGJKF3tRPvF7Vzlp3hrs+2B3KA5sE9fN152DC+bBK7bG1NGXrH2UzSZihFcYeL7XNR71MfGoLFQP3Zt1n2bYMP28QQcncL10JN6VYMU6ATvdZkeRt1WFUu919a7/Sj1PkqsoVOdPKFua4ezOi5OG9VeSlW1AbWeTqKEJFo56boRGkGuqiL0j4PW1WU6ed8MCclhUWArFgAm/aGh76sxiZC7ruDc++yFkUf0EdffzXa3qHnfH/HfH/gZm6LvDa0jXkJpxdK/PowK0Atr3xNnkz+HYIQQsdsmpq4+ZSaBFiNpKFunTkjIfhG4hI2gndoP0bvhbbUdes6E6zaB4hb1/0Hoxkn0I+6TblqbFieYiHuR2aNsbOrhsRabp1Dg0P1bEUEAeYFAtGIJge9eOpppsS6LhTA9fvuJ4lfJYJqlVBy337VjmUJqg3XG+5SzYBwddaRhHa2l+crCutRU89mxyoF43E7JrU8b8riyIhXF8SPHkg7ZxbNje5YTOcUz1xoejyw1b+QNVuV6IkOc4kAaVVV7jpAGg5WxCmY62unekj9ufMhilSMrahw28hIBCRgU2iv5cVWjCNbN3qsjmV5a/Gi81Rkaa3wr+y0RCYWk236IyAgh2H0wo6wAN06tN/SmqwPO0NsQKqifTGrU64+ktwPuEChptJGOZ6nLwy+6uv887bO26uzaVDIjN0fpWAA51U6Hew5PZIKlDgu4AaY7oUmeaFVVdKEmgO59rzEFRxIjHcE5O9IVyt3tVIi9TOcRuiGkvLCTB+pjmQSzyvs/ugq27/QQFA2l7Wr9Mn31zEl8RE5EMXLA8YJlgVnbCtieurZX"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14011","langCode":"en","question":"CoBehqZLpZ5Y3KcthqDStpFELFmX0LzAsGZiwXGURhpDL5z90qmCpb4ojUCqanqFVIC+wjrbN5po07yMmxwOEQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["nor","so","or","until"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/Ig/YToQYlTlatWutkO0sc2xm1yIxZN0ribZI/5ddzEUTkmdbNDm7tN4XVvzceHnD5eWM6ApvBBFcB8k9X1gNnJr+AbLHSqVCfBMxJlrszEgmwgxpXS4RoRCZWBr0e+jokMd0NaDURSwY/5QJEajZ+exBx742vYjBaw2hB5qhcn94TIvztI62EpqhP/HC/+Ku7k2QE24TsJyPw98BZZVsSF1ANwcS027idOljQkcT9h1t73ap1t7+L6pF2h0+DqGVsgTw8xnKRiA3K28ILtE/Q9J0I9baWehIVYk0dXbtJvRKd6zgBTW1t4qulY+yUpF8g2dIc5nhc4FQSLIkb6Dc7/yW39kAgSgPAV/zeSQZI5JXJphA+DBgZ7WSobb9TqYEGAuPeJPv4Ue2ldQ5rIjg+5ZLNqmTV0JRAsLyd5d0HTnNOj73T/zvrXjovwMY5sPPzblCcfIBZXB/lqDWrWfHdruUCRMcW6gz7W3F5MWUhOSLw5+yVJaZLxkJPG/pG0HULQJntg3J7k33L4DqTNei370xywDaKcKxI3J7QS9WmBCsUoNeQtDDpX7sUGUoTMFZnOF8oqXQCcb/ID+Dk2IJ+FaYqBlxThuliVP6YLGvdhW1i5PBrvb2k8t1ak3Ed2eP/MJPOu4sIpC3fQGGMwjp2w8th7eQn0cdSSOPrZh363QNdiEuPpAq2bO1eWIv7F6tqYQWGrQDlLw9W7YIyMQGc\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14012","langCode":"en","question":"H1wSfdq1Sd+aralW5eyhBxdf2zlnewtzJcvsY+LeHGlbv7D/gU00j4IjVQj32i9P1hdt2i/VT7v+/htmzqMBDQttxrQBhDae6Rp1FNuGkLA\u003d","answers":["yet","but","till","so"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12RqaPVVQj6XkcwNOeL1CZRgRKnZ5A5ab/vAxE/MnZgmO680JsdCe0VftUnpz3k+aTENLltGu9psBgwh0ja+hRHyM/Cq/aVOATvvbQ4BMQ/ueYFAtGIJge9eOpppsS6LhdwnqglOAB6Yq3fD3iWEo0/J/UPO8VkmFiqMsZEIgS3xNxX/dGYYvJOyYw3xasOo7Zsn1ROXFD+lFk2+5RMPIJBVu+mrfRts2MbNqzLX8k7xlBTfD9UOxzl+pmN4mrFXPMiNXuBDVkmQk6bvAvcGqr6YP7QOsow7BlvrkaqXZsGdb/VJ3m4RpdIoG44OoHxtrMckwiDDzIkbshQOmwNfhWrSES/EUeaK9503h64LStOhVVXf79FJ8GFJkxG5dWHDcdxFipf+SysbvJa0GLbOg18fGcyDMx0/SmtC2p/dRBztA+cYqmLYNvxnb1YFFomJvj84tT/6WQxsN6J1eLrH/7clZ0pGDJR7pEuYtDJK+EPF"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14013","langCode":"en","question":"mnCbKjXg3CBy1OZ5Dfpghi6J7vEWzaPWPV+2J++vh1/3QhFuBXw2eFCC9PITRvf94B7/OUawkaNqvg568qGtPSkFHMw+lzLI9YJKFW7r4SFoYbWNpcAXS7+anfg8lHj8","answers":["although","as","until","but"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16Ma8IiMguAsXo+u9KMJJyuz8DK4FNwntRCy/pTgIV0XGJx4W5lPOWkZUbRVgeYtjik3m0UQ2pllxdQ0nUrgPRfL6kXFj5qk36wOkYW9bCQw50Cw5FMJG6ICOVe899Inm+VPCY9LzKeJnqNRe9sYiRczgzhLeimigVhdKZTkJVoHbW1io3c3Z0G3WjtCofSU4A+HU6jh5FEnr5EVdCykqeTRriAaJEgd5oDSkSipz646+2Xj7q5OasnjKrBCfOwKrEBlZ03U2uxEzcncP+RHjnJPTG5PduOifnVE1OCP3uLL00xk0Wir8ClDqFOTG1kffTx0ewzeUn5ikmLuGeM97x4ygX6FBNR+HaFhgkuSf2T9T/vn4TQyr+5M1VcWeemihOhNMd/Ysn2YTVJU9ELddCwKZolVuCMGglfJnV3lRPHb90fi24B1kWK15XolVDPSf6IHoqRCdym8o2Tsh/AozaWYjL8oRqzU60m5+mpW1DDVY5lCaoN1xvuUs2AcHXWkYT3jvS7+g2R/KyM3b69XJQM5koEpNh0B7uPP+qz8FhAm3QiQrl2FK6GSGRM6ll3PmulfKatM/1DhPTzRujCm5LG+T8l7W64tgXgFOCFjFeNRkGjiVm4CwdPdkHanG3Ic5Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14014","langCode":"en","question":"ROdWncgL+h38kdQao3V1d7W7CX35Ospgas4OnEs/u/UM6RbQDiiqAgoaVN6xBVcP","answers":["or","when","where","although"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ6MtClpwG/m7ZUYLpjnKWxTxxant05UUl/Thh63hdFj1ymNArTOv0+Biq6DGks1RTi4O6i1fVmcYEobODoGRS6IGgbYds1LfUFlC+SgzCr+dFUIDOjn5YSG6mqGK9jIlgr/O6yham9eFyRj8tCb2sk9rDNin1r8Glls4GulfJ68gEvszMxuZne00Naa6Cl5FO7dzZVRmKXrajt/RygWLOPWRN78kCM3qApVaSOSccCd4CRfjTwRtbhl9/HrqQchDUUg6MTF3x4v0zv8efVozhw35Tvqja+pvzs4kS8sRfuLRI/tdTez7vejpxt4vgsOo5GMvXbMAjMQeY5q1IkYtyb7x9L+IWqcFTbCjz2+LIyuuuStFwLBx8NiJVgMvTziDGLm85WP9mYoFRBj+Tnna6U+6dsnIgDdRBahtot9WwaqTY1UAEf3TUNNwnWaQgMQypUixc3+EOhW2uCw/DqzLkrKZ2fdY+WtVvrLLLjfqRlh8Nor/HG4MSx4UhAcAUj/nmKLjg0kxE16vMbIlafIXK1zKnni51YuotzBiCADu0dvmOFcOzZ/OLXK3rIgnrUZ/4C5f+1/UDSFkvxdMmZB2neWXA0gpWTOn8os2hykAbK20ipEEVl/wL+52A/GTK+WoVU1kJP4WvCFchxNg0Ky77E9BCyxQjZDX5d9a6kAkATooXe4CmKE1fZ+IzjpjLoZD1q4p2VgtcxU/ZzyUjbIjiwLrwmPKnFcyK76MZeqaatE1Bq+mKgkMlENpIl+JxaD94VttR16zoTrNoHiFvX/QejGSfQj7pNuWpsWJ5iIe5HZo2xs6uGxFpunUODQ/VsRQQB5gUC0YgmB7146mmmxLouF0du5tnTK2Yr7fYe07C9re7Wvt0lgWFhfJnSCp/soNH6mLmnmOsG4LOw2H37vBQG29MCFcjRs6JbNZNQZJoOKXefHcSYQ6YorPyGq9RdomrsuRbm1rQd26eThBPsU90LhaFv1dZ1ktwdJdg1HYVPx+nGkujHORCOW3o/pqsaW+fM\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14015","langCode":"en","question":"NzBV6uxp7xbmh0FJGUhccZoZj78wuZrpr/d8NFoHu39pyA705WsttuSb1UAd8OOs4kHw6SOWlEz4Drep+7sMHzTj+e0yW0u8My0lJ2Do41M\u003d","answers":["when","so","where","yet"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/q/TUImsfQUxIS/xZY5xwquxsg931lYwkwMPPQYFNYJSmcUnNFTuasrMDLU/RFZoOhSizL4ThzPwB3YGLFQ56v1bfwdLgzo0+nOz4ZjA/57CCLa1P/q3bdo6LpqxZ/9CZPCPNknV1EJzHE9Unkm4bOPfKCVAwYjbs0Ytzb3EP920t2oLSwxFbRrzHJrFmIFFMVv5A1W5XoiQ5ziQBpVVXuOJYEVfttdBYcWgg57SQBqsUTe/JAjN6gKVWkjknHAneBMIpvUkZSsgr/tsXQdh06n+QByjOjvxv8qW2OezZlWTT8NTyLySpbQirQNzKPXGNsmYuVNFiA8RaUGyMk66rbWP+dhFDph9TPd7BGciNvRXcfS/iFqnBU2wo89viyMrrqQOwWomslrFuHqrNHIRO+YC2oeT3+GxB60Qeh5BRLyPcI82SdXUQnMcT1SeSbhs49R5qJPqz2gDzrnhpNOKoI5ET0Yl8WU5aisk/a/sFKhvkxWW6tHCJobrASZLWmpxLk0hsMhpb5hzhPyVRVffgUUuTaGVEP9zrN7COT+siDsgOmA+CVG2aTxYwQPh1nHuElia0ttyOhTObN6QzRgCoem5qdcByexR6WgyY4GTIK4vKhHfmxqju21Z1c9sRCtRjkWo4FF3EVHUiREFPaiT3Mo2DxgcsaVjP4KrNRTynqI1PrjTLb9u4If08wPqaLRBo+rr8RGM+WBdH/x5Q8tzuNV+yQ6JzIoiKxoojO6P1/GhGaSNxzXC+CSizbuE7inQvAyndFBsbOCxcZf4b4EdgMOzfA7+/LBLlRB0e09KqEsK3cqeImVhq2l5VRPP3aWCQc93X2SdQSTDu/HnFa+3XuqjM1nffwTvkcWufDfv24mAA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14016","langCode":"en","question":"4DeBGFWQ/YXZEzAGqfiFpeEWm3L2ppImeLqI/MCPKl9cGyKLG4/jh+7k/6tCOPA1cDQ2qA2DxxOIs6UqBglqjcZ7Q33VIJ53mNTm8jlRGnI\u003d","answers":["as","as if","for","although"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15MRO5h5hFtSQqs2Hk2HrAUa8Ek3BrxwIVOuWjQGyzaKRvKioIMTO9AC7qqM8zEC1PBekpDqRotoqrJfiuScXJIxtg2+DURs48CtyoP6BaaeE8VW6/e8n2thGuIk+YbQ98+oa6FAEq2qi4gOR+wcgKsre3Hhaun00qyuxWetUaq9ZLTScUdBcy1gyR6n4bFgUF/ow/AjzjTVz71e/5OOcLwdzyJ8qijnnfLVe35lXYKmMt4s0ZJWLO45ewxF6xbMF6IMNa5jXfXNJH6YFDybZJQ/N6JQKiElR3IMtGKcpR0X+R/3u1NV3ahoDTRN/vatW9iIA4SjWHlsexjYrCjmRJp0U28usIfWWDnGKyTTDs2YbDwDCO67P4Cyx0TZkatJVYmjbrvvabs/QwzzX3N5Ifs56kHPh6bS2vbIecYPv2hx0dzmLAlrTHTP7L/DBkJVprGgYQknrDbHtn5zM1WVevkXQkqUTYc+g+GnbhiG/0gMbYQj9NHQg2T9DL/yHfP7cOPlTyXljCaJgjH73AFzKHboTufyRL7Z+9vF7oDxEiOEbJLd9aIAe7NN+SBdUX+OPzryZSUTdSkOT5osFQg4wxacIdfl4ns87P6FZsKFSO0O/4cp0YEK74uAa4fjyhWv1gtAjwhm46tfPq2B9gy8o2AlSNQVQRWWXeuKEoXAkD/kXIrse4lu8zxuuiqS1KtSCX/7bDQLXO4pfE1256ca3cgqifyfPlIAjcyvFN6oFIR6J4kFCvbJrAZMXWTV9xbSoVVGJbB+lb7BByNYK+/w774Tzt75skxeU6d13uAiAPmUhh9nQPOE6Q5k/3hL9IycLw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14017","langCode":"en","question":"jKDa+AAicF5cDbYq8ggC++XsKkNXr9G2yJxiydgggWELMQzACvnZdtQgaWrOPL7i","answers":["as","before","as though","yet"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x156BIc8HdFvwK0HFVCARQ2Uv47JJKkYMMjMcZUVhfzcXqhbodBPCO+Wy72l+d2W66TL5mZ2cNK5U22VWYBFYjVCKrcnrOUj4SVpy0tBU/1KBeoGQtVvupzTCQnezaRUkaO04xhAlKbTK5mJ3U4AtMNdXdEZksELsmE2dlXLzLZhip02z6P/GSq3Ien6VxavxbWJRR/6dIcbiSbN39klQj+9JO4vvvF6v8dNUvKslXwDGmAh91zufQgRVu0b+d3wENVfYFqERvF4jx9yj4juhh8ATwVv6JsziUH2ZQUeY7zyY+Fv7FsdrpK0OsK9vipCbxd5rVPzhC3wFy0QxdkPeqSO1sexTSvGHNKuvOi56ZK3r3npPyC+5kwMYAGSXYq+FcHvfpg2eqjg5nrEac8nCtx467TL5nrI7pyg9JbMP9arVhjcZiY5vjw930H8CjgritoENRLdnYoSLN2TpkfQQ+cCaHjYYSjtMH8uTWb37ECMJuvezF8x3n8cjZjuU787Du+BUSSvBNztdYEOUjO8Ab3lS/lDkHHqWoqk62zhnlAe8Yoe+SnHk66L+u5c+JaHo8TuvNCbHQntFX7VJ6c95PmkVlvaKmH04qjiNZVKg4iGgY5HuTieFTRem9Ed2O0uauAQDoqFvCRwhABod9DSzT5w\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14018","langCode":"en","question":"kwsdZb0IPd0c6uHHdfFh9nEaSG/6UPCYTXsQliYUwJ8c4TCfUCCGpU/32st0+9Zyzfzl4gyeI6fmsGPjGcoHdQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["as long as","because","as if","after"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1127MyNcmf9r4+J2P7MPHolgViCMRi2Lqr6Oybr6oitRgid4fJ1WMaF7tGwmeDdfVpML6nG1BaRd6BNVA5Wej8PPdimsiLt/2ozbr9hRatBz2s5+TJbXAq2PL9bHTmucAdgnqe/lg7ADOffq8Eb3EI5JPxBEYNYS1s2tYbUshBs0oJ+b9XX/4TPRN32YqelctXv6uPH4LjgXIXiFh4pTpEGL/oOdiocX7CqGxFCJ1AQ8Pd372S0Ejh6J81r/xE8jgQSWl8ozHJH2FiNfH77aWh558e+Uhrt7wiOIMQk4jzT+yimz0oewA33ugDrArJlDJpN8EkJe8trIbIQmkDdVtYLePmy2uDitMEu87e4nFZGzZXep5cdJTrEuBMmI6Zxb0IsT9phCHiB8Bb1btoK+0h93Wqyl9LJz8pm/9yFj3P4ZELDFkJ6qMCfTxmOrqfOPf9/OlAkOzfxPPZx6DHbjdsDCxjmp+X8rw+snCstaydRAmgBQVaTtZLSu8ykk+fXz8LWDX7XsdYxgueHaJMhRw36zewSViwezogkstsQOiEJM5iDTxRvAJmMepYixfC0oBH7hjTyq4VotaQtXVbH9zHQXIq0gw7o/mtGExOjBWqrjziBuK3+vIsj3T0PPpVHj2AYkH7UoknATmkDn47soPQ4O7Sx20/7dO1I1aYJ/0NTH"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14019","langCode":"en","question":"I274LV2KvWgGta6L6nmsMUIO0cmyt487pX8TRcCHnBGglNPMg4/TVkFYvkQtLV0ONQ0D7WGPeagcVAnToeV8IQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["as if","so long as","before","after"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14w8+cU6QP2EgVCa+HCHBGdgViCMRi2Lqr6Oybr6oitRMUIfjJJbrvpinRUFtt3aVJML6nG1BaRd6BNVA5Wej8PPdimsiLt/2ozbr9hRatBz2s5+TJbXAq2PL9bHTmucAdgnqe/lg7ADOffq8Eb3EI5JPxBEYNYS1s2tYbUshBs0PIXb2mS1RMki/C/7P2qpbtocQfm/GhqepbfdxvmcnuiED8V55ZPDpX5rRJEi/QL2/v22+70iIamfTWSW4mQ7Sn/7MeNQziyQX6ssBUQnd9gfxTeuoSA1uHawqx88d2cNYsAiK17J3rUNMh1aXkYQcDoJtSaKdsae0nBaTu9AHDe21YuYkDqSYZPR1rmZktCjygb0/HQeSIn3Bj0nBvLN6FLA0deWxC8q+/C4dKLIOhNLRyKEljgdddjrVD5d6j11Ez6YAAfbKvUZD5yRAQ8OjLu0f2TDp/iOtSxUttaXM9rjM/qlxJ2CrgF5qNW4gPlAgQ0BEjgu1t83ln5OD/r+W3JEBIkjgSrnryaDs1iPG1V+05btb4ll0pXC8Nd7DrlB"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14020","langCode":"en","question":"jUaK8qnB4jebS/f/rnmrSNfcajPAmd6dIF4n4+EnnPaWJc6/lMcsrFqpxmV74uVlenbcM66GJnV0jKeP/3Xrrg\u003d\u003d","answers":["until","because","although","so"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xGgUdWdquLyTZfRIL+qWLb3wRtNI4JIg4huQWXMPo/0hy/g96fw2dVNQcuYsoW5qP87rKFqb14XJGPy0JvayT3b47smvfYH2ZCR4K3UubViELDFkJ6qMCfTxmOrqfOPf9/OlAkOzfxPPZx6DHbjdsCtA3sIuEu1SjBMP/0MA+T0cxnklup+ZkVwzTomMGySZPwZYDxUtfu7vtsc+PYkQmsenbnkEjY+9DXjuppJSOQr+Ls2z324N843qsAo3A7P66BSOYPWP7a5HglSSidL5GhnMo/H5hCil12zRVvGckr1df0nMJqXe7TKChkJirM8TmaGbYwJ3NR8l2/r9xVBOwDOvR4dnWJpsuSSrod8YI3vp+XQbTj5KBwIoOct6xw3fkmIjzhd6DLAmj46RsnAJMDmOJHqF87HmkWcMYA4IHG+qwJmlJl5x5NpuFEYdG7T11I/Y/CWB3n+devoYIz/1ucLj8HGq4dtuPM5dbQB9zqD6RgUzaXqR9wEpETGyDD60OY4keoXzseaRZwxgDggcb5SttTYXSnHPikMTDLLDA+CYn6IRbf4S/14/LkD8ddssfD4+MBTivu4OgaV0LNhp5X35CXCCMOslXRPLmdwgNq50t8rD60Rnar3t1RPHpXiw6MZWxRLE9Flw+yzTdFPvxCsoxpeiWwWMBFS32WtpJ1d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14021","langCode":"en","question":"VGaSbA10lKsmA7zu8dcOhYisvdAGEUt27LkXFJIbm7nede9o7/OTyQzNGzm+aVNt5vk+NhIJupUmsVedT8ms+g\u003d\u003d","answers":["till","for","although","as soon as"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w64MCubrou+2OzVl4F8mCVXfWBczaBhtwlFwSnCr/Yz70YemKU0WSi5qJAVbVNk9jRxhtX9PKDsHyC1GPaCJM0lZ/otIq7/cpKRxFJeY0+b9kYoC8DZN9Vy4MdMTiXhWXDwAfrDymu1fJYBUavPdNtz8cnwaruM0I2ghgxSerNEwSpivBq+zTlL+qrJloQFh0BlZ03U2uxEzcncP+RHjnL09X64U/50LUEoH1nlblC5DTQLmbTXJDbeKiBGQcO7UUI4cURJWeXfyR0oAuyOZlxAJfcfnNxBPyMeSggOhkDAACMkwJykBw9pKEL9TVNRkeuK8Mk42lzuHw7hszA36K5L7MzMbmZ3tNDWmugpeRTuZkOci4PxLbY4F5hvfIaw1E3jc4lU5Ozduw4nJ0/ETAbGyD3fWVjCTAw89BgU1glKseUZk51C7sW0L8MrMjQcJoXWv4EHecaHpiUE/4Gx5pfvAicS/qmVYD6JrkK3bY8y2U5/r6j9WafGRi6Fl8rsI7agGtVh/dRrX48k5ocHNkLKeizlCEBdiB5HsHJhWwq7z5B8H7mONL5y7IyCk4twTG21P1hwKbvXmz21HC+36Erv8jzpusO2zGzDM6CJDmcmZomtPNXKJK1/eaBJuU+j2o1zl9YPnDnmdfPr1XnAx7vfPGOTIxdsHLF3y0nvDFQAXNEqh5JM7FnQUGi11+Fv1OWSEY6Fp3Xj43wcsnNoNx8\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14022","langCode":"en","question":"1oQeovAOIe/Twlrgs+v5fAE45MCsiTGSwY8n5yupXxSSHUiAq3rz6j+r5q5QKbRXfuZklZu9t1YXroi5ML7jZgMnbFU+Ut5gHec7j4vmXyo\u003d","answers":["yet","even if","but","so"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+eKe6rWq6LEM5kebBO0f4ESxqJ/AWEAdF/W4d31dviHTyQDGTMmGmZYYtIEAtjHJsFG+O/Cj8nYLNGPhm5jw6TXcEK2DOrkBf/u/+betgs2U/iTx7efO3W00aMx/6+yB1gj8F9/UVIG4HpEnDqdZ9EQbcITc8Gz4p4Z/vpHdYh5tEp+i4Kv2bWfEEEh3bM66tDD05Ha/ui1Uu1F6MzadRHWDvttX3TgxrzxZEVPZ5izBT9wyBUfeFVGpJDlPDA3N/fG6uKfLiGRW33juMgjIosoxmAkvYRB18nIOJfKCZGeM7p8k5rkn5rXpDN/poGz7XSSfEPoPYssCJhg2TxpAYZmrZiZyxyFtBkl816NWmzktVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14023","langCode":"en","question":"so+N1VqZ1tcSSJ08n9EHbtiprWcqQ2Qf+gXwTvvziXitBeQv85CeEI4yrkGEwIz8iwTN9aC1jc8ZLTmN3NRCfg\u003d\u003d","answers":["though","but","because","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wyZGeXuAmSKgf72lUi/BLWzq0Zxpj08UBqfwV/bbg80s7DAIFOH6i9olYUrkFQYnjv+zoRyNJOQfwt7ecpaXDIlJvladPf/Jiru09s4dQXK+Ls2z324N843qsAo3A7P69OT87wpOyLk63C7dHH7zjxLWurHhG3gaMh188xZzOawP69D62RQkmbXEndmzwQI73Vq5ECBh0pWn0uHwugOQeMAbk/EdAcM7I3+Y4BsWY4TorOZmAi7agCBLGGsaMn+1KFVyb6/QduM01cemf84zA/c387v+V/OmeKdNVM6voJ5MOywA7OJxOb/eiYpms8Iy5ba0xwfTuZMrWV/eft+lWfrxPME0FBfSzY+LkVOHNKRZcciQfL/nOU/OzlSPr++2zhynoss26hCUGS4GVni0R7z69rR55EHUW8vKUJooF48RoEpDaN/Z6oVbaYWC6Is/OD/V7COsLtoyXISLwlKmu0sjwf/IePwqTq33tEzMv+ZdUomRnGKKJ/7DG35H5hIW6GAUv6aDvt+7BETzo0++Hc6ReW+vddMlh8cndedyjcwj9WIxKI4nFaiWBAwoxC0Kw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14024","langCode":"en","question":"KV51xbxvSXOGfjRFpU2ZeVM+4J6gNnR65+oNwLHI1tApjVdN7z+izV1GcUvNxoKAbtvdk1jYh4Qo/1Te6UGSJf+04+jI/Ut4dP0uYCYLqMY\u003d","answers":["whereas","when","as","until"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18q55z3jxBp3RWGvcoS+yMB+bR1shz6SzPDZsOl56Bb1Ez6myVe3rCQ9cXlqP1rPSGfB/2lKahuqgMVtKgsg2F9yr7IfI5lVuXfsLzfuO52B/1MSrT9g3VpKXRAa8cwvvWziZVsgWs7KEhfm1Vk0BGUcdFbuoNP4u+LU5mvyv7PtYgkHwOa74+/MSTxnzO6OA+mFd3oqHT/0wr17Ak02KX61WWEipz9umwlzCVMV7CEJL0fPU2dAN8NoVklTyeTnEZmQzPShrs/DJgyFNT7A3RR6yyK7cgyUhNdOiBo7s/RrbxCG/ogf71SWemUqkaSkgwFat3Dkriw2eU4Wb9tmszGLp/gr9BfoEPBC/1Y4hNKK6E7n8kS+2fvbxe6A8RIjhOAOD2suL/PpCaryXWR6T03pwtMPR3M4RzV6QQ2mvczlZJg9LzwhbagXo9E0u6xZY/tq/AjUjTdK+D0ofFBooEmPV8mRO584L6WeV/yhjsKqb+QNVuV6IkOc4kAaVVV7jkIwC5ok65giOYrMuuR5Y5MxnTIa0Nx1ZSHb8fm9MKdDei8Miun0C2p49FM+ELluRXGdoEV6kE1tUtpvCxczUpGBIhgKDfjp2qUJLc8jarc6boGHHiyVteSyVRj17ZEi3+XkTFbIcceZQAAnyb02dnjxXgc6CG5BAS1CBzoYDPJUMHs+Susoq5gCpCwxa6YKyu2GXGO6lUnfTdEpnZXPRXZrZiRhoJnFawc9Jl2xuKwaAq0K2NYrfjS66CQkGNKAF3rOPCcu6CVQeIh7Z1i8H5P+Uwg8Stk14cPbbJoEoUrdcC29JWmz6DPvClzMylje0DuvNCbHQntFX7VJ6c95PmkxDS5bRrvabAYMIdI2voUR8jPwqv2lTgE7720OATEP7nmBQLRiCYHvXjqaabEui4XcJ6oJTgAemKt3w94lhKNPyf1DzvFZJhYqjLGRCIEt8TcV/3RmGLyTsmMN8WrDqO3Nus3SDkMLyg+Mi6EtJiZE"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14025","langCode":"en","question":"t9c0bQc7t7R/ZmGZSKk34R0vwJrgcTFQ17KfYKXlaV72tCkJjaWMFJx7fpFDiu9JXSKhgWTV/PdchdEEM0D8BA\u003d\u003d","answers":["whereas","before","but","when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ6MtClpwG/m7ZUYLpjnKWxTxxant05UUl/Thh63hdFj1ymNArTOv0+Biq6DGks1RTi4O6i1fVmcYEobODoGRS6IGgbYds1LfUFlC+SgzCr+dFUIDOjn5YSG6mqGK9jIlgr/O6yham9eFyRj8tCb2sk9rDNin1r8Glls4GulfJ68gEvszMxuZne00Naa6Cl5FO7dzZVRmKXrajt/RygWLOPWRN78kCM3qApVaSOSccCd4CRfjTwRtbhl9/HrqQchDUUg6MTF3x4v0zv8efVozhw35Tvqja+pvzs4kS8sRfuLRIKqOYgyXCOwxwUJ32+Eete/l/MILp/koeZS5isH5yEjR5HmM3ViPlzgIRU0fbVyMNEGYYlqUc0FSW619AXKlvuCVnteGiXpPNK9lv7ClrownYb9OSKaamSnspwD80aVzrQ/MdAvWS0oW4J1BnViVzWX4zrrf4tm+yY6r2kfU1LKIzuOKSTmYxBYy4JxvwSal4N4vyy9vlVDM5B9EJJzgRUAFSDdM4u7/RAzLDPAWkgCkufUdRWcndGX3YacxNe2i51mNeR99iE0J/SDmQrzdhlq2/nwyWOtGQxZ1ZPXAJiyeIu9E1/d+TgZM4GaL8qbXC6TaGlMXFawFepT0l/KwQQWKIla/HIHZ5PYdyh60imxDfVvfCbXIcd5x4W/kNTgEz8PQIQ+8SJsj+aLIcOPT4TRvZRNh0OR22Vg+LkpWvzm+GNc3PSHTn+e3jxIIiSw/CHMKmRtcBBSMUy/vqpzDn8\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14026","langCode":"en","question":"GqBHTv0XBnBU7zlu4rZS8/O9MlvZDhKPqZYCa4xO9niyXEWADj+lnKCKo10RicbIOWJR2lwUus63j8Ngx6n8xk+G/lXu/ybOXbVZiwB6vhyfHrXUo/7IbhRgiixYtxFa","answers":["after","as","when","while"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13WoWOEpRkx1z5fbDtK4lZqgCpfvC/zby2/8UlQcDBmXYnaUK5rKs41nrr+5DMs9vy67G0M3BnF701zv03JDNJG9aZjQL6RRUNy46Scu/YQNl/9dvtz08O+bPW/31XAkCbEXN4fBNXaDLiUHtxoGEpoI5QBCxNzB/DvKmra5E1uQ38Ccds5Ss1nUp1DW7CbX2NFQ6rwmP6fz+bOWHcHCcdmrQcrXf2LIONIZ8ZQZKPcvH4ajfISPVbGM/+x+mCe4Xes9V9AbjkAq7ADf8jJE5GnjeN0GmcEzA9lBczIg/GPbIMwl8sLbVudrdcOPA/azDqcij7HyMLz7YWyhSMyccPUC8iQB70QW9JuQl8YsNFr7LWbei5R75/uWKmt1pphjcQBfULTMHwFW2qjy4Z1fX89FocJaYCxZs68QJH8Ah9xD9LHDbgMyG/agDVlLj/gNMI2dO1LWb96pA7WtvouvEFCWgV0WY1ZftBurMae+h/IqpyKPsfIwvPthbKFIzJxw9a6NkUSI6u5q5wLk7Ee1BUa+4aRaNKrePk6Q5ixG3wamDMl3iEzPA3NoDEsLQRo0q+Y4keoXzseaRZwxgDggcb4z+VmNP7bzV7aSCzCfAgG8WLsfb3x4B3XpZdlouLlpPAwYL8i5BJXH95AT7xjdS03+RwmcyI+q+VbG2n3TtPxTwYIdTFU7PQSX7x5xgfsU3PBlv3jmOnvvSUhIFao2VWIenO0HwdNwjv9lRO/RlhwIEGlL6OGekdiEBYpS5pYIR0akZ0/VagruFCzqbXRehH7uvXizNR0SOs1KMu5p3HiOIxf5BUeUCVafpgMsyFZRDoTJ6VVYSzLy25Ba81z81lg\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14027","langCode":"en","question":"x3oValem6oqP4m6pRcfns8o5vUEBpCehpl/oP4J/9/9iyVjzSrQUObItm5FJi77QHGOkp2Q5DLm7QS/hFT4fhWDckuCzLtLHPPdgn6pSdi8\u003d","answers":["when","since","until","whereas"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x10exaE7c9ihfqAQpFUOcLClLuWcdL8EvtMdnbo+4ng8xIxt5DuS5jQBA5w9Zhh2tNU6IQ/BVqwnOY1AdzONAh58yTxNs0Yk3++0cNYksn6zQVkdWNErOwt7zLBaByZo2n93+2WKHJX9hYDaoRRBUqRA4vG/TePCDU44CGoa0GGLtLdPFLnD2PUmfSfw/1qbxvAkKmQLJHke1zSgvsFLLPMhYmMi6MDS22m374A2OEIEwQftYvxTFSaM0mzfop1KZGBIE+ZNcfIFbdq3+y7pmgi3bmtdD+rM0Ew7xiu3P7hw8nTHQ0neBg4coTp8qrVugCaMptghUV0PNK6SbOw7X9oi1ppPD3cGy7l5ojoZ85x1/X2ZmptQ6FoE47Bny1aqajmCD5n1gjFY2Z918yLVeQ860PzHQL1ktKFuCdQZ1Ylc1+2iemgRAH9L7WqXWDLNjj1U5i8sZNpTDrF5jwkZRNzTNQIIn/wOOpOXqO3m7Q0tx5cIGsgnDLXlkQWu+Nl8xn1a9Hzmma1H/pVxkLVPOg0ErSvAW1Xie6gNlT2/Le9IIGr7FDC4unr98IwDSSGaq+IT5O6ZQno4T4vIuAeZGDyafraSOri/zRi6BvdtMCohJb/3N+QiYIxm3CyQujCUz6gLOLk0ri51qH17dDzzsy8GldzctiMxQnI8KKVetEVQIg3ByGD4nMI9kQATmroTlQvTXQeQy+2+kxwCcsUxNHXrP3FhH+xYeCmeNunOqqV2fcxnklup+ZkVwzTomMGySZPwZYDxUtfu7vtsc+PYkQmsenbnkEjY+9DXjuppJSOQr+Ls2z324N843qsAo3A7P66BSOYPWP7a5HglSSidL5GhnMo/H5hCil12zRVvGckr1df0nMJqXe7TKChkJirM8To1XCtcbocryknbkTkO7yuo\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14028","langCode":"en","question":"GUJZXHYYTvr/NI2i4lg54cVES3Y4rsv1lyxUP1ODESa73y9JqXlq4sFoX+rav81rJR4uv+jRjmBUH9OpwU3v6QVUD9i7DyUxl8AAjRL74p8\u003d","answers":["either/or","so...that","not only/but also","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1/f7L/7w5PktKxg6X5gFuEf2TG4LCd+lOnIAFiZ0SdRpUQykddiWgcuvA8O8uI5L7Mxi1rMVdzIxLvgIm6H8Sl5pa14LB4UhiF3Qu9EK/19o11mdMoj0oyrL52Im/xT7ytgvYcu75x/8FtFfmlZ/zlk6HbWwNzMoEgBvRZ3pQwXrqsVLfrjHBhy7o5I6P+v1ASKb2vEOT1LiZgc8mnGiXQoiUsHOTcpj488E7ZA+WYFFdbSqi1+stomegfV3yqfxhTo+b4rDkzDDVicrzkVw1t7ErW8kBpgeyIYbQlbZhkoL3b6WhTfFUxIJXDjvAdDocY7EhQB8UFjLn79Dkwqi2g1AWLx4YoLPFx7m3Agm47/ROL+TjWV6dTANrnB3TD+8Zml/rDa4UxgeBKPAlS2NC9Q5dJ5X9cqdz1pyLRfIAs17Mgm4E/xOXJurSV4myjtvVOKCtk2Vx5FCpAQDU6xALnBzC+cqAmhLYGEe3YivVWlADhono0QHza9T5pddgubHbF/U7XpSuRcLUL8XlYtWjxFLS6UpM06Fdm2HckxO52vMJYizovXDIJ/LB71FgYMrRhhz0nYFAheZMiVhj1Qw2ys\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14029","langCode":"en","question":"5KM2mgkv8CNVLLJTLxjY7zibAQHI5Q6zNCxBH6aOuXIbjebX5DlJtXNfNyHC/4rfyLTec06FoZMdi5FKD6FQCA\u003d\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","either/or","not only/but also","so/that"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12ObJKY3kN3P2H4k0YTnAoG8KMxBtGd+6ZLJ6tFHQ0wwWQYrNR5CvvnzULnRtYQX4ACWFCRvYA49m5gwpWlBshMsJmQoXiGw7d3WIiJVpmruJpKoN2581GroDUY1v4QHi9w23GtNetBd5wgMOWZOkxn6gAZzbSfbAtALBzEFxqK11YdSqSRUQ4j4xKyMcCpKDmzV9LWHkh9OXsfcs8vdKIk+1v8u5e0XyJciuEvLw0W7/JwH+udduWnIMP7idV+9QbqFoKPtoec3iJftrrF4QXE1y9yistWm+EPtUgD5ckjFLknRpEeO550fHEhgSez16BswNsWjdGLItbpdpPUphBGJgdtkki3AOh8+h5RjPImuGB8ow7j2s/1GsNlvBxr1eb/TJXKUsOQ+EP2mA6tF6NRijAHE3b0rVd2E0p0raEn4mIL7W4RWnrMxQxgeW+bQa19aPCIu/VgVKhdrQe7SyDIft6aTQItUdLEt17CHusLFvwfpRVTSkuhb5arhDZ4VT+i8j+13gTzvd4it4miKEfkwEyspA8TI8seenkUlOajw"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14030","langCode":"en","question":"IFaR/zHCjqKdg4yNiGPjhHyISAHL1tYMdqdtJmS1Y2QWaxLirUp3jYyshj/x3ULZ+53nDBP1DEwdiE3acv0PbA\u003d\u003d","answers":["not only/but also","rather/than","neither/nor","either/or"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11KLOJm3Z+YGBgS3ICKLzh91PE/WBLfuWTMJFu7fpjSK+zknuayWfAVrLK8Gi/bvuN2iEgT1jBaC7WNBP6SKWT3WOBN+uvEmEp8cQVzDexn7fTtfuGv2PpmeG3HMDa1WdWGHIXI+U+eDQeA9rLGLkrzlXFtdgpRYEoRHcH3bhvETIRtj5SAiJ2/KZ5ggH2bIr3zfA9iiAAzNygDG3/Ntq4qct/DS/a95HxBxAZeAPP5kDw/B9O5y6q365a4UO0dPNPJXQv+06TQ1hy8VVdDr0ON+IFiq4qVlP6RwcKJFTiE0DbpGoa5yhVnwSvHqt+C3cydsceZ9eV4jPQMBOhx2P+hQItpUow0ulCPa7d8Iq5h+VGAWXv9/iRYOkntVQM7HIDTWGcKmLCzHN8cpaKtCd1zqHxVmjj4vz6BVBnLIAgDyQwbxI2O+LRgNecbQvInvGD1clV6J3XocFwdKg3CRFHu0FYr8XZEpFvsLInnL2yx/SSwEFqBxp6qJdyH8sq/HurVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14031","langCode":"en","question":"2Q2V0Af82fl82C59VLqoA5IRgkb6j1HxZ3eXf9FLehbffMP43yHCXxcx3XxIeUWAhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","either/or","rather/than","not only/but also"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x140URuTv3RPNfyMRLB9vNno/HGZPypG/uO6rCA4rXIr+fhfdPjGpSKO5/PpSWybh944iI9X9qpmusknohPkoE0Xuc/yJDjYw4W4RiqEMROr40zGPsUZAbiBf9pIJdJEj2Ub53makS925c6BxX4/RCXXWhPCCy4jKl765enkpxRPusLSEmvxuC79gamrQjeoeG1x7uWHohZK2dVsvMDH2ZhXXwNWlY3K+5BoiwmYbizHnLXMgAPZEfDeUAA8RQv19VHGN8xQVxJITA5WHiZktUPemI61jmBc+B19MsyZJsaOAjMfwlGBrJsoAbxcrjWvmFXAx6OMVYQgl0qt0UOHURBcfAwAchQKqpstJrzs96b+XJShrGYGm2rVBaO0+AVOKu6mtwVQ/+w03uKeaMBe14MRs1fS1h5IfTl7H3LPL3SiJPtb/LuXtF8iXIrhLy8NFu/ycB/rnXblpyDD+4nVfvUG6haCj7aHnN4iX7a6xeEFxNcvcorLVpvhD7VIA+XJIxS5J0aRHjuedHxxIYEns9egbMDbFo3RiyLW6XaT1KYQRiYHbZJItwDofPoeUYzyJrnqcHnsLZNfk0BuW4xwqK7A\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14032","langCode":"en","question":"ZwrQqOTM6Kgxwc9ZECi5qQIu/DIl3V/6O4cmyq0EDiRNSJQQy0HfTaRPqPjTFt4OhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["not only/but also","neither/nor","no sooner/than","rather/than"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+pJy9ak22G3vDRAv9SfpYgK49538iqMLSes3botq5LVKB2C1bBcYsXDo7WvYL4q3wtQgZr9MBSxcej80PBV2ekWm3+UWYZ7OAw8Tl9sECs7Z7gKbZh3+L9+RAbPRcY7r69qXoJroUqahKrDrLRQ8DEqEZmQ+YlDf4k0GGBO530njbLb1n7fcxD4cs6fhoAzszd07ImQJrOry2Wv56LS1Zz2uJn+QNrkead0L29cq9AOkqpskhnNKrdjQFEPfEc7fVGFo1yhoHi2hXU27gGxs5sAAp+3TZmX6t4+vAUX3YxSw9RysovFzdkJVroE+LQTgusp4sXWDacxf6Cj3MDaQmm/QiV7TRJYUf495Ck7O6lf7kE3ahWzcyFzb25W4vAyUDLE5dUPiUYd7u9cpqw2Hk6kROOYqHZ5lhUXqVN3cfbqDw/B9O5y6q365a4UO0dPNPJXQv+06TQ1hy8VVdDr0OM29eZlQF9aDDe1MKY8+t4S"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14033","langCode":"en","question":"T1b9VAKK6rfOHxbOVE/1yNvTVhWnC+2RLZneZqr7RUdQxjDPYBzev0+t3UFLSW2o","answers":["neither/nor","hardly/when","either/or","not only/but also"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yTLPqkbnEe6uBM5eiS/iRPD+SljaNSrTr6N6DJM1qXsRtUKQgWRgj8sh/rxdVxvfAb2WfMV00eUegEK//syVUOOX7nUlLcgObMUmWCFA0vB4Y/XElyl+TdgHC9jrrH4+5mCxK/87k0RpMf542TNZ41v256Cp8tnhJTyI3h/7sNXyg9IuzxPrkH/2n9eyCi0V0AtzcP39Oapr1Lw4MDJFZLzqiqNOZmMLdRbWmrIuTP2ChpTLTIBZNISThdhimZvcJ22vOTF9pQc32+HnwQF5213G5xNHnI28OjgQu42OtuDd6ExFCuov3RkBg1/c+lKD5DAkAAVgj617tIdibl3f0lvoukN+FJ43AHG3RbRbhPBBh8Ilch86eDAcosW1YuMRe9nCt74tMj7F+jECIGENQTJ/Qv3I0/ciOjK2FwND+gd8lfBsOEEXLm6oFHnkMS0icR+krpxDRI8ZVM20eGxSNwEtMCOSsvfM3ydGDXeKSL5VD34AufCfmS0yvU5/DWXgQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14034","langCode":"en","question":"buHE6fB/8P1spCtGkKZeLgrjn+79E3eP9Or9PiQskIhYgJolEDAXkhYFdpdMwExwJwSP+IzsbfVDRkdZP1cgNlSAvsI62zeaaNO8jJscDhE\u003d","answers":["either/or","hardly/when","not only/but also","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1yTLPqkbnEe6uBM5eiS/iRPD+SljaNSrTr6N6DJM1qXsRtUKQgWRgj8sh/rxdVxvfAb2WfMV00eUegEK//syVUOmazZqXHteO8ERRFDpeX6cn9Ci5x5cfzV6uLO2cUfeMYy1tEpNHncAp2W/jYWaiu+7oR+20a8Osf4wH3363spbJ106IByrsdx7oOPHY57y8uGP1xJcpfk3YBwvY66x+PuZgsSv/O5NEaTH+eNkzWeNb9uegqfLZ4SU8iN4f+7DV8oPSLs8T65B/9p/XsgotFdALc3D9/Tmqa9S8ODAyRWS86oqjTmZjC3UW1pqyLkz9goaUy0yAWTSEk4XYYpmb3CdtrzkxfaUHN9vh58EBedtdxucTR5yNvDo4ELuNjrbg3ehMRQrqL90ZAYNf3PpSg+QwJAAFYI+te7SHYm5d39Jb6LpDfhSeNwBxt0W0W4TwQYfCJXIfOngwHKLFtWLjEXvZwre+LTI+xfoxAiBhDUEyf0L9yNP3IjoythcDQ/oHfJXwbDhBFy5uqBR55DEtInEfpK6cQ0SPGVTNtHhsUjcBLTAjkrL3zN8nRg13iki+VQ9+ALnwn5ktMr1Ofw1l4E\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14035","langCode":"en","question":"0dfQ9JkovsTMGDZR9+hHQOvCnSaCHt/it4EbKvCP4zY26sh/yTIpMoLE06xOqs1HPlBQluXtu2KM1a7whsr1dJkcbpviGeTHSz6j8klorpQ\u003d","answers":["rather/than","not only/but also","either/or","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x11KLOJm3Z+YGBgS3ICKLzh91PE/WBLfuWTMJFu7fpjSK+zknuayWfAVrLK8Gi/bvuN2iEgT1jBaC7WNBP6SKWT3WOBN+uvEmEp8cQVzDexn7fTtfuGv2PpmeG3HMDa1WdWGHIXI+U+eDQeA9rLGLkrzlXFtdgpRYEoRHcH3bhvETIRtj5SAiJ2/KZ5ggH2bIr3zfA9iiAAzNygDG3/Ntq4qx2SPZJFKGBjJPf0yFg1Gu7zU2wD3wq6K6JM+Ivxlf/osG62TFhjCCFX5C6j8xNHN/FpafBZmK2xhwiS/bquVNy3Nr+FKPpSDtK/zUxPvfabDgGbp5Utw4BWnq8Mm1oDQYTBGh8e/Hc5KS3ic5gdXi2OZhe7vclRoEbkmHEAeqSPxzbdOD/P0nghHqVOrG8qmLtYEky7Xnd1TueZpoK97HQ/BBc0WrfLIUHDAsB/JWwuo8UFlIpVz0sBBdpJeeM04ZPnJ1pqENHCgoOSM/6QF17rJrWEx0PhYkh/gETFhzecOHH2Gr75ajgQt+t3VplHwZ6YiFWsMqC29FJhXagXRjlyGp26sec9IVGGtb9TKTOBWoafe/U0fRDtfmtUMpdK8G616549WHUcc8L/7crlOL5Df6m8IClxOA/7MIQDhg2Inr5xb07o2QYqL9DsqL3zQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14036","langCode":"en","question":"MPDfx8UgbCPapRTfIhTsFQFqO6swQR67eyWi+m9RGUvSzhAa02uji9WVZPpOXPKNdkeAYiLDJF+Bg1mqDLQua+J1vSS44TcBf4oNAoNrYmI\u003d","answers":["but","yet","so that","or"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x171iroXu1nBW/B2aXgpsVm/Q+otW4bDtcCG8cbK4YLRBc/A/6vB6QwNXhI1ndSVn7hmp+S9d8fkwpMyQt+P+/dFwj9NId3u60r+3Z9hsKiXix8RFfPk6DuWALjUkt8edl3D50PpqHI5rdLR0g5oRFE0eqgLhh1Bh7pS2wFZZZHH6txnOFyffitij+9toYMOIdszUlwvbyEvATWQ8CFb8DIeSK6siXykyX7gJxR7zC5r80NsQKqifTGrU64+ktwPuEChptJGOZ6nLwy+6uv887bO26uzaVDIjN0fpWAA51U6Hew5PZIKlDgu4AaY7oUmeaFVVdKEmgO59rzEFRxIjHcE5O9IVyt3tVIi9TOcRuiGkvLCTB+pjmQSzyvs/ugq27/QQFA2l7Wr9Mn31zEl8RE5EMXLA8YJlgVnbCtieurZX"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14037","langCode":"en","question":"YVhf2+tUxQMupYI/8LFX9znimrZSGWU6/P9OC4iu/Gfr+ecRzy3JBh2MfeFMiQz134JS5T/N1NRtkVZP0W7JNyXYdW94xJozx0XVoNLnxyBKYj5G/T5+mjqh6hIr7E3LKMvrzxK/nOA9a3ImxsgcSQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","not only/but also","rather/than","scarcely/when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13/CoJ5y9MKD5oBKFiQmelW+F/Hmo02nIGdpL6FBu2qUZYsCAcAvxnE2ny5J+8VhlnuYjkXI9bcsZO4pfcdiZ60JezRvEs895tiaHyWTowIun5synxPXjGjPZR/TT/xeYaSctR3eP1SfjJudntC2R6kIuKvrpIMFHT1BR1fd4gIj9E+Q0dUD0FqtZOHx47FAO9gvYcu75x/8FtFfmlZ/zlk6HbWwNzMoEgBvRZ3pQwXrPvwOfQenIdfy/5nIv1seA+yepjzAv/9WCcXkUftjyiHF6r6AvieKM6TGKXje43hUx6v8ROU1WUSI80eKgNl6IaEtaFpjkWktHmKouBJi+b39AyiCE6RBAC56gDydOvffCZR8xuxlaQ8O71i3SN+BSw4OzPdut+5mm2oCsVqxzPVzEX1gi12VetWQPD+3BslNyAiHnIgPSjWPh5MEo3iaNCKEUYtAY0kNCX6eIjne0rqjnkYyLo9M3tA+JWWgPpX7"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14038","langCode":"en","question":"mi1R5SeWyvJAun0E6fjtvLrnld8alfRsfhkaCDfqoDMTqIWPBc2vrfF2lf/9/WzkBhSmLSlrsvw+m1bE1WWTrFJpIdl81eUck5vHE0wqIYo\u003d","answers":["neither/nor","not only/but also","rather/than","scarcely/when"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13/CoJ5y9MKD5oBKFiQmelW+F/Hmo02nIGdpL6FBu2qUZYsCAcAvxnE2ny5J+8VhlnuYjkXI9bcsZO4pfcdiZ60JezRvEs895tiaHyWTowIun5synxPXjGjPZR/TT/xeYaSctR3eP1SfjJudntC2R6kIuKvrpIMFHT1BR1fd4gIj9E+Q0dUD0FqtZOHx47FAO9gvYcu75x/8FtFfmlZ/zlk6HbWwNzMoEgBvRZ3pQwXrPvwOfQenIdfy/5nIv1seA+yepjzAv/9WCcXkUftjyiHF6r6AvieKM6TGKXje43hUx6v8ROU1WUSI80eKgNl6IaEtaFpjkWktHmKouBJi+b39AyiCE6RBAC56gDydOvffCZR8xuxlaQ8O71i3SN+BSw4OzPdut+5mm2oCsVqxzPVzEX1gi12VetWQPD+3BslNyAiHnIgPSjWPh5MEo3iaNCKEUYtAY0kNCX6eIjne0rqjnkYyLo9M3tA+JWWgPpX7"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14039","langCode":"en","question":"GMugKu5OQqvA+1+/o4lLTfpqHZV9n7fus2n8WvZY6uE3XoIZNQRuaYDzteHw+ykPKKi0ZxKOOUN8VCkVYDnQgCTJooiv7UsxRd8Bsm0GCTLDMorISXplCY/wGUOSrTPd","answers":["not only/but also","neither/nor","no sooner/than","rather/than"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1+pJy9ak22G3vDRAv9SfpYgK49538iqMLSes3botq5LVKB2C1bBcYsXDo7WvYL4q3wtQgZr9MBSxcej80PBV2ekWm3+UWYZ7OAw8Tl9sECs7Z7gKbZh3+L9+RAbPRcY7r69qXoJroUqahKrDrLRQ8DEqEZmQ+YlDf4k0GGBO530njbLb1n7fcxD4cs6fhoAzszd07ImQJrOry2Wv56LS1Zz2uJn+QNrkead0L29cq9AOkqpskhnNKrdjQFEPfEc7fVGFo1yhoHi2hXU27gGxs5sAAp+3TZmX6t4+vAUX3YxSw9RysovFzdkJVroE+LQTghzsKjBf0kES1Iq7LWK0+4l2UPHJthD0MqZbFg3tSl2RFBv4Knij+C4mH9l8hYwYXic5Xcl0d/BoAnutnvtz816nHWpyYP0Aj5u1BbIBY1PZDAEYzl9w6/aOO0Kku5DcX22YmPIuPmWLlC4ZoZqONv6QfxCIa2K9dI022AFFxGeyTIOuVaoM3guRJb/szDE01TU/w2gHdGUua494LOKASxpew0xjq8TsNcq5/pJ4LQub"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14040","langCode":"en","question":"8gYZozxXkK6BhtJ+QjRjg3iv7ouAfYhpnSDEHUy35WCUyzrlA4c3/1hEHQNMXO2o+ijSS7Bgmu67WG5w7PLk5A\u003d\u003d","answers":["although","until","once","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15hTNd/1FZPjEhM6Bew8XvNWXqQugtVJY/LkVXKDFLMny37cBD8fN5Jx1ZvueEbO4n5m4drt1Zg5QNvyoEd7tDkCUptWBQ1C4aQH/0ODVsN2boCeTdV8UXfWLkgimRKPSQzhTWL+42jrJyPOTfMKBXK5LvykdX0iR19dN26tjZEIN5rCVCfljkGcjutq55mezM0KSmjF4k/2OEGeJQsa5c+n3/5OgVTDEQeol/egz3Y7MNZZegLvIfjcBww+hpq/f7KmkzYYcOUdqTcu+3hRNw7nb/C7IgDPfdnRZ6XISQw8ReIF7hFtZKNr3DxF+r8z4OBOg0nko/0iRtN7NyPxukMP3jiNsBQMuL76NGnKzu3+zE950lwwKT0C0ecyF78KwUXQeQW56yaiaMHQQCYua4Zjke5OJ4VNF6b0R3Y7S5q4ofPQB2+0xChQN1rLOAasGVLEOYY7FPGsULHbTUI6z1ChUH5j6YUnffR5tYt3ihPLsc6bNzo6DlQ3vwfEw5vehRPL0fINoAEUcHQiX4IGPNx14f4846xaZwRSngnWn22rM9kPJGPxso9tVym3QJtUffWcP3+Dqq6cRT2GdU1N+qiNaqqa+fbUu14t6kl9hejlgmwgxpXS4RoRCZWBr0e+jnfL3vGVGZGokypLjdgkHAMeX4vwTH+tLFAjX8F/xPsv5JMmk9kotPeMR5+JVXZfZiakbbDnjJfCQLss7kyM7MEAbk/EdAcM7I3+Y4BsWY4TorOZmAi7agCBLGGsaMn+1KFVyb6/QduM01cemf84zA8UK3kcePk3vD3gXUx8yl9HhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14041","langCode":"en","question":"6YzGs/EEx0AgOE37V16H0GctMvmKrx25bAe6AKQrJ84AP/W8CDZgV/FLpgguW8nUxM5qQE7uuXvTWTe+NQAZsJc1jH8mkUN8gjqAWfiQyw8\u003d","answers":["in order that","but","or","yet"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16damW7QqhbuhyCwDJxY6Svu/hXJkqtRTjE3PG9qS+dUEHGxXLJ4ZV5rM350iy00+U576vTK0Yw7appd0Qi1StNb8dRYAVjI6GKNm2p+BSSGEWGS4QhUUyqACX0dbArUgSVoJ+eCi9f1i0VCuGHjeQdEYhivK1P2YkKDHV5GLaconTlpLQZeA5//atpyAuBKUAnmz22vIOjVR0nSwE/7/+7kPi+ASzywp0yinT+OdTlckNZILolhee/JQIaksSqoOcfH2yfkCX2JYKejzEjTeULJDK/BqSWLzDGXbw6vAGNGYJDiChSIJW84Ap4XgVHdaE/IiVWFvdn2rEKYF+zZovX3pCP9t1YrezyyO3XqIxkLCLwiSlQyf3KCggJpdC2ZEZTAaTZG0Aq+X02eqlBjyY7ZkceZ5pk5FrANsOsP0h4hqgKWigtKbnElgJGHOifseA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14042","langCode":"en","question":"cZH2FxRMeCrijrH7vaxjeVwzw0idVzK/TNceWN3iGO84YPa/itb3rI7T0/t3Sdv1TgNcd7kSDEixVkcP0qm7GFXicNyG9VXZMZi82XqW6DI\u003d","answers":["and","even though","or","so"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x139XmajdgPkeSVlpuzhiYGbeV5lZir3Q7tVUBLFI2TxhyO/ugDceGtS00JZ56qbHqi31uno2qQBTc4BcSLF6X/I9PiO7k5/dYuOMXKNxPhO08fnFM4PAblJeOsQbEb6nL1LEOYY7FPGsULHbTUI6z1AmPZdVZMVnWEgJu12U+S80S0ulKTNOhXZth3JMTudrzJPALbRfkhzxBtjKimzH7Dnl26alp+a69uw+m4mGKqnNIhFjqgV46Oa7hTp2DsSWZYuODSTETXq8xsiVp8hcrXPfYus14xCJc6W1yuF82eSWD8/QUZBb32quFvBIqOHpi9LfKw+tEZ2q97dUTx6V4sOjGVsUSxPRZcPss03RT78QvpRbzlo6+9tdaIZQRWojVcQTXV9Icb5tg4sBbBUxHv84cn4tUx+ww8mIK/ZpUb1/hsf+aFldudxUlOiqakOdXWeA3OTeBvZtav6wmmKf1fmE31zQ6cZn/QJyjwhvyYPbRKd6zgBTW1t4qulY+yUpF8g2dIc5nhc4FQSLIkb6Dc7/yW39kAgSgPAV/zeSQZI5JXJphA+DBgZ7WSobb9TqYEGAuPeJPv4Ue2ldQ5rIjg+5ZLNqmTV0JRAsLyd5d0HTnNOj73T/zvrXjovwMY5sPGF/NiHBuMubUCzHI1kWpgA\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14043","langCode":"en","question":"XHh8ZaTn8DinqjuDVrHMQpWOIJf0YQKCNH+ZPnhDOcEoxi5DZg1Zoj+9mxuUfy7lbx684i2YRXVQ7rT54PpIUWJiEzYRQf0qzvTQQUlhex8qcYojpGe2d9m1FVb8SSKf","answers":["rather/than","such/that","not only/but also","neither/nor"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1z2dfv1o/Y6J3Te0t1KSQIxqX8TkCcVa3sBnriPPQITsX9WZAH1rcfQkUWquJTqyBS/WQVbykV3hOyOLDUb4ycPXPvMobpIGwcdUpEuG41l8Cm42JBfE3lb1YGAgC8J0WjTWGcKmLCzHN8cpaKtCd1w1X+dPZkyIWQWp1B37U5+9NmNLaVL158PWAYRDKArR1mmjoJj1Whdqgalxsph0uY9O0tF7eMfWVNXXTkTafftPke8i70zcYnhprcNu8PG0BObTeBRh6YJygdseoTnH4DkEs6Ho+tn06IJU1XG7FcOikbOAwA+ZPizuLLWFwFRcNXdarKX0snPymb/3IWPc/hkfwL2FjSC7L74LA2wJc2hEP+0e8Bmw41JJxUV/t4RdCIx25FxF1RLBbuAruOJ41eun6a0Qetj2IVEJUORvVR3CL2SohcQnC9M5mEfO8lBq/DzwtlLm20nkPKlY9JuyUcK6BUSczN0yjV4u5N/XblO8"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14044","langCode":"en","question":"8bPMfrCBhXNwWMU3syZrDYLtdmnC2kE7VUJEV511oGRGkzVv6Cx1My/5pPTYoAFFVCLMeFdHLQuamAL1RVXumQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["until","in case","so","nor"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12MY7jiAVsxxE1eVbbro08LhB7ZrTTzXOizyey3w//MYlpGyZsQ1XusC4CBVYGtEbLusZzVs/Pt4OgYms0PMLl3UXTtBhhrfn25oCZP42R8PfUXTnd3hhAP84dflqfGwHFl6Iyx8VHgic5v90+z7DykcDUQvBOnqnbDlyuT22nm/j1vghD88nr6YIUb9m5pLGvWpg0Hr3LuRAmFesj5l1wllhXNR88qLvYL/fF6isJBjAWQYhFWcJ/EmkBYyco2oQnMZ5JbqfmZFcM06JjBskmT8GWA8VLX7u77bHPj2JEJrHp255BI2PvQ147qaSUjkK/i7Ns99uDfON6rAKNwOz+ugUjmD1j+2uR4JUkonS+RoZzKPx+YQopdds0VbxnJK9XX9JzCal3u0ygoZCYqzPE5mhm2MCdzUfJdv6/cVQTsAOsBnuAxU+H22XkburihqzkmZwqyjcglKB7vX0ijoxAYjEDrt3+CAfqR8QolhMaXTtS6jrlrbBTdVvHP8FaAj6iX+5b7BTCn5eDipW2VN+Q8yvrrOddHI6M4jU/5qpYI/uU7AWD8oKGn1jUCd/U4BLQFOaXW84hzymJ5zVgANy8EFjUf96kChObDIsYFXLZ7mf7FkqutBwXCi4oTxX3Ww30w1lrNKoRP1eoDeynJ8SZo1/0L2imgiJxDLck/CZdvo"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14045","langCode":"en","question":"xOv/56pRrXqi/fWVealuEt8iLQDWxqQ6haTr1mZ9YDZ45+V/BdJNUriAM3p/0zcd46xti0QWxleWZn+LeX5g0w\u003d\u003d","answers":["nor","so","until","in the event that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x15q6ImuVyuOZMkdvnJ64yXgTBjMH+ODvfXuKE6+/mVmVcVPeBGN+qmnUPva1lOvq36Dsc3NyHA1DkdG0WjS+JY5F2mfaEJzO0ZrA7T9QV0pvw19O39vJH+npD1B+xihoOY3zs9bV2hA1UUkWAlemOQ7wPy+bBDSU5roQMZ4NWA/x9fdERxSlkF2NNIFVl2N6E/rPMzVJGKrehk/tViw6yGQcBkJnk5xX9LHt07NuP6vnPSjzBnPcukVqVpAWqbXKjK36igW8vQmFskz/ST9BcnWWFwLfdJXRGCFh1i+HaV1QRdB5BbnrJqJowdBAJi5rhmOR7k4nhU0XpvRHdjtLmrih89AHb7TEKFA3Wss4BqwZUsQ5hjsU8axQsdtNQjrPUKFQfmPphSd99Hm1i3eKE8uxzps3OjoOVDe/B8TDm96FE8vR8g2gARRwdCJfggY83JMiqPjtKT7oN2B8ELCN8WmAOJI14wUxppzi9XrxUkcDf4hwlhLTL1o+N1CMcqbKqTF4cHiHTR1ut5T1wO04c+OpinRUdMkEkpRzuCD2C0IMRMgUIsVPA+1hTjLmXUQ6Uh2JEI4e9D9Roa6tvaE3jU1Qktwk2S0oC7SXYen7VQZu0KDIHFlncTHCug9Y3hO6uAOVIkWGhEdOjLjc7wMXzQ7Za/0bx0akhcL4E1ZltGPYDkCQ89Hzd9idtVLZ9vTq3w\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14046","langCode":"en","question":"n53gTF+OPgbXxn/3MvGF8fkz7Z76Z+vJHPb+VeBixwYHl+VpeWxUS7V39aYmM4YHtLGoTFSkpc7mxDzKJrSVRTML0/gixbMkhj/yrr29GxQ\u003d","answers":["as if","as long as","after","now that"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x124rKcOKv9VsuE28Vb7DcJc5Yzm5mkBiTrX2p925Sel5VW3yOjh2bZGcbgm2WM3n1QZkyrFaXSlemZRk/j+4Qr6q+0/7qpg+i1Dt+ysTJAP28ZNgVOPaWM4A0XvgeLaLlO69eLM1HRI6zUoy7mnceI4jF/kFR5QJVp+mAyzIVlEOiGbs3dIctXY6B7IbRFPQTDObYCmzUOGyeV3dmGSBhXcZoIodFmoTbe9NTfeqWuc3Ubnu2qdq1400X4ggCM/bbuCE4xFegAhGY8nOfnVxqpksXgzELkCvLAmbFB8aBlkAddn5fxqSmNTCCoB1A9QnoGzR3YIU4BFn0wZPfXNuG+25w7130tGRO+s/NHoQ+VE08/fssspxI+QTojHRqqV2ASHucss70JzKbc/ntUYMMYb2nS7JeHZ79Z9TjN0n6O9SnTZajTJCweEh4dLTuoc4HMK7zlax8cp25ABIWzs3e01KN/20G5B7nrSvCbNhovzlE8VW6/e8n2thGuIk+YbQ98+oa6FAEq2qi4gOR+wcgKsre3Hhaun00qyuxWetUaq9ZLTScUdBcy1gyR6n4bFgUF/ow/AjzjTVz71e/5OOcLwdzyJ8qijnnfLVe35lXYKmk+4zhFZ44ti+DYzhv7sr8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14047","langCode":"en","question":"CIcgmULYV+JLBhoRQeRnDf4DniWAtPV36ne1bf/1TBDLHcMhC9IPeq16djiNFGd+","answers":["but","after","although","so"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xAAXDi/5hzT9A0ce7/ML6IRuOX3/LTWr0c4xpCTkeMFx86Mcq1tf+z66ysISHGlfDYFed+nvX5pSs9v6ZNN9HgrYyDcssFX+WnJvjPidyrWBeccW3YPkU6XQ9Q4weRmcaZBSs2eFDohoNZeBQuC7A06CQK4VkBV4KPnfGSz8ALCaaUtZS4cxzAyQuVtFLoSpzv+zoRyNJOQfwt7ecpaXDIlJvladPf/Jiru09s4dQXK+Ls2z324N843qsAo3A7P6xMzWlbrxqHphy+fW1ZkqQZOf1kc0/Uq4axsxUI2sqEFq7LX7iSA0Y3paNOtbwNM/GdlClxXw4RbBSGbJzZRXn3/O6yham9eFyRj8tCb2sk9qWBigNmIvi+iyjiazSb79ubIzz7S+vLcGirDjp7zt9r1/aGDa7qsOiMFcBBQGMHMXcbgxXj7rrWYVg0y/JSBhKNH3qmo8ctJT/0pat2ObUUteNe+I0K4CKxoKMcJF3GlqX+S0uQS/w2voaflk+VSrA\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14048","langCode":"en","question":"2HhL6UvKFUzfiN4dEELnkBLtU7PVY9kWJcBMda7qE/eT8z6xW++6j0dJLLnCem49bM7hLia4OUIVmPkK/e5InA\u003d\u003d","answers":["as long as","after","as if","because"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xGgUdWdquLyTZfRIL+qWLbhK3pe3q+QIK/nLsuBAr4nboMt90bsgsEHvIuM6YA1NjzOuorqTivHFWSXdKbeh/Ek0Wgej+iZDJipn/y5jnQMpI2A9lfrmY0fvZEGSr4isodPeeb2C4VUf0u/K5mv1ZrmpHw/1xtI9GYqBuuRvUMe7r14szUdEjrNSjLuadx4jiMX+QVHlAlWn6YDLMhWUQ6IZuzd0hy1djoHshtEU9BMHQy+XYqW37cvRyeCg0jXuvsKDNHmVgtIkVETdghidDpB5CBsmaB3L0jQpeHq7yHo4xL/Yg9mtdVZLLpCEs4bk9gws+6n/fA67MjzOYxEE0k5TST7EiGzpo2FLbjdhnE9y6XkkiuIpGIzAv6EkBP6g4YiIKPfybx5yRUtyybtVgOwfymhRoyC0TuxZFQqtoEQUql9Egonwc8PdJSXUoFV9qvIJ6cL4EQ8E5vTMq52AzDAKXDzdNxVE/yYr9hQXGy+3qQ5SotGlxW+hXgQFK8EXA5b1QUK+7xEoxr8F/Vi9RIlstfPae0FOf36t5AJ4OuNouanJdmyofEXfPA9K2WcdNX2UPQNwxzAmXj3MowsKKvey+m8s7w0Y4N+jf0BhWfokcxdEgAGjk6NtQCwAL7k0/QDxNWBL1m/tldj7w1uZek\u003d"},{"topicId":"14","id":"14049","langCode":"en","question":"uMQEAykPKuwi+vdwwCXk6PQYnaTDirttUcG9A6qA9L2ivSyYJN6MPHd04sHVR/hr","answers":["yet","for","or","so"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zEY5se+v2aHE5Ll54mzoouttCi4mha9QNr6kLe9sJAgtEp+i4Kv2bWfEEEh3bM66tDD05Ha/ui1Uu1F6MzadRGTGIuVQNkpaa4chY/NZ0iax8fbJ+QJfYlgp6PMSNN5QskMr8GpJYvMMZdvDq8AY0ZgkOIKFIglbzgCnheBUd1oT8iJVYW92fasQpgX7Nmi9fekI/23Vit7PLI7deojGQsIvCJKVDJ/coKCAml0LZkRlMBpNkbQCr5fTZ6qUGPJjtmRx5nmmTkWsA2w6w/SHiE1P9b2yVF3yGVcml/FRVdZVTmLyxk2lMOsXmPCRlE3NEWhwlpgLFmzrxAkfwCH3EOpiCAqh3SFU1OiFGPnEJaxkk2dzkQhxprwMq6iuGQGNBgrZ7jryRFGWhGDPEnpYhDrJuI/0tOiftCEV67pP+JiFWeJ3AVwG8Ncke4hvANaANHeECiA4KGlBvHMCcJiRFTjOleIzmmry1TnnWyiiCLZEACltxTktc5MBsuJLRF+KHE2SyomkiPgs4R9X3IARQTmgdNS5Z7T2eAhKGrOkzG4isd6BhLAnZRFFjQzyW/zyQ\u003d\u003d"}]